Grove Press Records
Grove Press Records
- Evergreen Review
  - By issue
    - Vol. 13, No. 69 (August 1969)
      - Editorial files
        - Arsan, Emmanuelle, 1969; agent correspondence, check request, typescript, galleys, copy of French edition (Box 872)
        - Hentoff, Nat, 1969; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 872)
        - Lahr, John, [1969]; typescript (original and photocopy), galleys (Box 872)
        - Lawrence, J. D. / Springer, Frank, 1969; check request, typescript (Box 872)
        - McClure, Michael, 1969; agent correspondence, check request, contract, typescript (original and photocopy) (Box 872)
        - Madonia, Gail, 1969; author correspondence, check request, contract, typescript (original and photocopy), galleys (Box 872)
        - Noble, Richard, 1969; invoice (Box 872)
        - Oh! Calcutta!, 1969; miscellaneous correspondence with Elkins and others, check request, contract, galleys, photographs from a performance (Box 872)
        - Selby, Hubert, 1969; agent correspondence, check request, contract, typescript, galleys, copy of French edition (Box 872)
        - Tyler, Parker, 1969; author correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, photographs, typescript (original and photocopy), galleys (Box 872)
      - Letters to the editor, 1965; lists, photocopies of clippings, etc. (Box 872)
    - Vol. 13, No. 70 (September 1969)
      - Editorial files
        - Project file, 1969 (Box 872)
        - Bukowski, Charles, 1969; author correspondence (telegram), check request, contract, photograph, typescript, galleys (Box 872)
        - Comolli, Jean-Louis / Delahaye, Michel, 1969; check request, reader's report, typescript (original and photocopy), galleys, issue of Cahiers du Cinema, May 1969 (Box 873)
        - Eastlake, William, 1969; miscellaneous correspondence, check request, biographical sheet, photographs, typescript (original and photocopy), galleys, clippings (Box 873)
        - Harding, Gunnar, 1969; author correspondence, check request, contract, typescript (original and photocopy) (Box 873)
        - Hentoff, Nat, 1969; check request, typescript (Box 873)
        - Kirstel, Richard, 1969; invoice (Box 873)
        - Lagarde, Gilles, 1969; invoice (Box 873)
        - Lahr, John, 1969; check request, typescript, galleys, photocopy of clipping (Box 873)
        - Lawrence, J. D. / Springer, Frank, 1969; check request, typescript (Box 873)
        - Lester, Julius, 1969; check request, typescript, galleys, photocopy of clipping (Box 873)
        - Oppenheimer, Joel, 1969; check request, biographical sheet, typescript (photocopy), galleys, cover from E-407, The Great American Desert (Box 873)
      - Letters to the editor, 1965; lists, photocopies of clippings, etc. (Box 873)
    - Vol. 13, No. 71 (October 1969)
      - Editorial files
        - Project file, 1969 (Box 873)
        - Adams, George, 1969; invoice (Box 873)
        - Arrabal, Fernando, 1969; check request, typescript (original and photocopy), photocopy of introduction from E-521 Guernica and Other Plays (Box 873)
        - Espinasse, Francoise, 1969; miscellaneous correspondence, check request, typescript (original and photocopy), photocopies of clippings (Box 873)
        - Hentoff, Nat, 1969; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 873)
        - Jordan, June, 1969; agent correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript, galleys, copyright (Box 873)
        - Lahr, John, 1969; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 873)
        - Lawrence, J. D. / Springer, Frank, 1969; check request, typescript (Box 873)
        - Lester, Julius, 1969; 1975; agent correspondence, check request, typescript, galleys, photocopy of clipping, copyright (Box 873)
        - Mednick, Murray, 1969; author correspondence, check request, typescript (original and photocopy), photocopy of clipping (Box 873)
        - Menkiti, Ifeanyi, 1969; author correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, photographs, typescript (original and photocopy) (Box 873)
        - Montes de Oca, Marco Antonio, 1969; correspondence with Lysander Kemp (translator), check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript original and photocopy) (Box 873)
        - Russo, A. P., 1969; author correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript (original and photocopy) (Box 873)
        - Skir, Leo, 1968; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 874)
        - Yurick, Sol, 1969; check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript, galleys (Box 874)
      - Letters to the editor, 1965; lists, photocopies of clippings, etc. (Box 874)
    - Vol. 13, No. 72 (November 1969)
      - Editorial files
        - Project file, 1969 (Box 874)
        - Carson, L. M. Kit, 1969; author correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, photographs, typescript, galleys, copyright (Box 874)
        - Hentoff, Nat, 1969; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 874)
        - Lahr, John, 1969; check request, typescript (photocopy), galleys (Box 874)
        - Kooser, Ted, 1969; author correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript (original and photocopy) (Box 874)
        - Lawrence, J. D. / Springer, Frank, 1969; letter from Fred Jordan about turning Frank Fleet into a movie, check request, typescript (Box 874)
        - Mitchell, Julian, 1969; author correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, setting copy (photocopy of another edition), galleys (Box 874)
        - Newlove, Donald, 1969; check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript, galleys (Box 874)
        - Rader, Dotson, 1969; check request, biographical sheet, typescript (photocopy), galleys (Box 874)
        - Tipton, David, 1967-1969; author correspondence, check request, contract, typescript, galleys (Box 874)
      - Letters to the editor, 1965; lists, photocopies of clippings, etc. (Box 874)
    - Vol. 13, No. 73 (December 1969)
      - Editorial files
        - Project file, 1969 (Box 874)
        - Berry, Fred, 1968-1969; author correspondence, check request, contract, typescript (Box 874)
        - Crouch, Stanley, 1968-1969; author correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript (Box 874)
        - Delahaye, Michel / Kast, Pierre / Narboni, Jean, 1969; miscellaneous correspondence, check request, typescript, galleys, issue of Cahier du Cinema, August 1969 (Box 874)
        - Grafe, Frieda, 1969; check request, typescript, galleys, photocopies of published versions in German (Box 874)
        - Hentoff, Nat, 1969; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 875)
        - Hoffman, Abbie, 1969; check request, typescript, setting copy (taken from another edition), galleys, photocopy of clipping (Box 875)
        - Knox, Hugh, 1969; author correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript (original and photocopy) (Box 875)
        - Lahr, John, 1969; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 875)
        - Lawrence, J. D. / Springer, Frank, 1969; check request (Box 875)
        - Lee, Bill, 1969; check request, invoice (Box 875)
        - Newfield, Jack, 1969; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 875)
        - O'Donoghue, Michael, 1969; check request, typescript (photocopy) (Box 875)
        - Oppenheimer, Joel, 1969; agent correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript, galleys (Box 875)
        - Sale, J. Kirk, 1969; author correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript (original and photocopy), galleys (Box 875)
        - Tynan, Kenneth, 1969-1970; agent correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript, galleys, copyright (Box 875)
      - Letters to the editor, 1965; lists, photocopies of clippings, etc. (Box 875)
    - Vol. 14, No. 74 (January 1970)
      - Editorial files
        - Project file, 1969-1970 (Box 875)
        - Adams, George, 1969; invoice (Box 875)
        - Amram, David, 1969; agent correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript, galleys, clippings and other items about Amram (Box 875)
        - Bukowski, Charles, 1967; 1969; author correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript, galleys (Box 875)
        - Fowlie, Wallace, 1969; author correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, photographs, typescript, galleys (Box 875)
        - Harding, Gunnar, 1969; author correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript (originals and photocopy), galleys (Box 875)
        - Hentoff, Nat, 1969; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 875)
        - Jackson, Richard, 1968-1969; author correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, photographs, typescript (photocopy) (Box 875)
        - Kerouac, Jack, 1969-1970; agent correspondence, check request, contract, typescript (photocopy), galleys, rights (Box 875)
        - Lahr, John, 1969; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 875)
        - Lawrence, J. D. / Springer, Frank, 1969; check request, typescript (Box 875)
        - Lester, Julius, 1969-1970; 1975; check request, typescript, galleys, copyright (Box 875)
        - Levinson, Michael S., 1969; author correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript (photocopy) (Box 875)
        - Rader, Dotson, 1969; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 875)
        - Stuckel, Eugene, 1968-1969; author correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript (Box 875)
      - Letters to the editor, 1965; lists, photocopies of clippings, etc. (Box 875)
    - Vol. 14, No. 75 (February 1970)
      - Editorial files
        - Project file, 1969-1970 (Box 876)
        - Adams, George, 1969; invoice (Box 876)
        - Brown, Cecil, 1969; author correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, photographs, typescript (photocopy), galleys (Box 876)
        - Gardner, Fred, 1969-1970; agent correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript (photocopy of another edition), galleys, copyright (Box 876)
        - Handke, Russell, 1969-1970; author correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript (photocopy) (Box 876)
        - Hentoff, Nat, 1969; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 876)
        - Jonvel, Jean-Françoise, 1969; invoice (Box 876)
        - Kandel, Lenore, 1968-1970; author correspondence, check request, contract, photograph, typescript (originals and photocopy) (Box 876)
        - Krim, Seymour, 1969-1970; author correspondence, check request, contract, photograph, typescript (photocopy), galleys (Box 876)
        - Lahr, John, 1970; check request, typescript (original and photocopy), galleys, copyright (Box 876)
        - Lawrence, J. D. / Springer, Frank, 1969; check request, typescript (photocopy) (Box 876)
        - Rader, Dotson, 1970; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 876)
        - Schultz, John, 1969-1971; agent correspondence, check request, typescript, galleys, includes copy of trial transcript, copyright (Box 876)
        - Van Dyke, Willard, 1969; check request, typescript (original and photocopy), galleys (Box 876)
      - Letters to the editor, 1965; lists, photocopies of clippings, etc. (Box 876)
      - Notes from the Underground, 1970; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 876)
    - Vol. 14, No. 76 (March 1970)
      - Editorial files
        - Project file, 1970 (Box 876)
        - Amidon, Bill, 1969-1970; agent correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript, galleys (Box 876)
        - Bertrand, Raymond, 1970; telegram to agent (Box 876)
        - Boyle, Kay, 1969-1970; author correspondence (photocopy), agent correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, publicity material, galleys (Box 876)
        - Brautigan, Richard, 1969-1970; agent correspondence, check request, contract, typescript, galleys, copyright (Box 876)
        - Hentoff, Nat, 1970; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 876)
        - Lahr, John, 1970; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 876)
        - Lawrence, J. D. / Springer, Frank, 1970; check request, typescript (Box 876)
        - Liehm, Antonin, [1970?]; typescript, galleys (Box 877)
        - Moffett, Cleveland, 1970; author correspondence, check request, typescript (Box 877)
        - Rumaker, Michael, 1970; author correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript (Box 877)
        - Sanders, Ed, 1970; correspondence, check request, biographical sheet, typescript (photocopy), galleys (Box 877)
        - Svenson, Steen, 1970; invoice (photocopy) (Box 877)
        - Walford, Roy L., 1969-1970; author correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript (original and photocopy), galleys (Box 877)
        - Young, Al, 1968; 1970; author correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript (original and photocopy) (Box 877)
      - Letters to the editor, 1965; lists, photocopies of clippings, etc. (Box 877)
      - Notes from the Underground, 1970; check request, typescript (Box 877)
    - Vol. 14, No. 77 (April 1970)
      - Editorial files
        - Project file, 1970 (Box 877)
        - Aronowitz, Alfred, 1969-1970; author correspondence, photographs, check request, contract, typescript, galleys (Box 877)
        - Buggs, George, 1969-1970; author correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript (original and photocopy) (Box 877)
        - Douglas, William O., 1970; check request, galleys, photocopy of clipping, licenses (Box 877)
        - Douglas, William O., 1970; clippings about reaction to article, Gerald Ford, and proposed impeachment; 2 folders (Box 877)
        - Douglas, William O., 1970; press releases (Box 877)
        - Freed, Arthur, [1970?]; notes (Box 877)
        - Hayden, Tom, 1970; check request, typescript (photocopy), copyright (Box 877)
        - Hentoff, Nat, 1970; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 877)
        - Klein, William, 1969-1970[?]; correspondence, check request, typescript (originals and photocopy) (Box 877)
        - Krim, Seymour, 1970; 1974; author correspondence, check request, typescript (original and photocopy), galleys, copyright (Box 877)
        - Lawrence, J. D. / Springer, Frank, 1970; check request, typescript (Box 877)
        - Lester, Julius, 1970; author correspondence, letter from Helen Wolff objecting to essay,check request, typescript (original and photocopy), galleys (Box 877)
        - Mayakovsky, Vladimir, 1970; correspondence with George Reavey (translator), check request, typescript (photocopy), galleys (photocopy) (Box 877)
        - Newlove, Donald, 1970; agent correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript, galleys (Box 877)
        - Price, Bill, 1969-1970; author correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript, galleys (Box 877)
        - Segal, Abraham, 1970; galleys (Box 877)
        - Seligson, Tom, 1970-1971; check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript, galleys, copyright (Box 877)
      - Letters to the editor, 1965; lists, photocopies of clippings, etc. (Box 877)
      - Notes from the Underground, 1970; typescript (original and photocopy), galleys (Box 877)
    - Vol. 14, No. 78 (May 1970)
      - Editorial files
        - Project file, 1970 (Box 878)
        - Brown, Cecil, 1970-1971; check request, contract, typescript, galleys, negative (Box 878)
        - Ferlinghetti, Lawrence, 1969-1970; check request, contract, typescript (photocopy), copyright (Box 878)
        - Hentoff, Nat, 1970; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 878)
        - Lahr, John, 1970; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 878)
        - Lawrence, J. D. / Springer, Frank, 1970; check request (Box 878)
        - Lester, Julius, 1970; check request (Box 878)
        - Marshall, John, 1970; check request, typescript (photocopy), galleys (photocopy) (Box 878)
        - Orton, Joe, 1970; contract, miscellaneous correspondence, check request, biographical sheet, typescript, galleys (Box 878)
        - Rader, Dotson, 1970; author correspondence, check request, typescript, galleys, copyright (Box 878)
        - Sumner, Bill, 1970; invoice (photocopy) (Box 878)
        - Terrell, Robert, 1969-1970; author correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, photograph, typescript, galleys (Box 878)
        - Tyler, Parker, 1969-1970; author correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript (original and photocopy), galleys (Box 878)
        - Wolf, Roger C., 1970; check request, contract, typescript (original and photocopy), galleys (Box 878)
      - Letters to the editor, 1965; lists, photocopies of clippings, etc. (Box 878)
      - Notes from the Underground, [1970]; typescript (original and photocopy), galleys (Box 878)
    - Vol. 14, No. 79 (June 1970)
      - Editorial files
        - Project file, 1970; 1971 (Box 878)
        - Adams, George, 1970; invoice (Box 878)
        - Bukowski, Charles, 1970; author correspondence, check request, contract, typescript (original and photocopy), galleys (Box 878)
        - Carroll, Kent / Baker, Fred, 1970; author correspondence (Baker), check request, typescript, galleys (Box 878)
        - Duell, Jeanne, 1970; author correspondence, typescript (Box 878)
        - Garner, Bob, 1970; author correspondence, check request, contract, typescript, galleys (Box 878)
        - Greer, Herb, 1970; author correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript, galleys, official certificate from British Board of Film Censors (Box 878)
        - Hentoff, Nat, 1970; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 878)
        - Lahr, John, 1970; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 878)
        - Lawrence, J. D. / Springer, Frank, 1970; check request, typescript synopsis of Frank Fleet episode (Box 878)
        - Martin, Lionel, 1970; author correspondence, check request, typescript (in telegram), galleys (Box 878)
        - Schneider, Alan, 1970; author correspondence, check request, contract, typescript, galleys (Box 878)
        - Schultz, John, 1970; author correspondence, check request, typescript, galleys (Box 879)
        - Seale, Bobby, 1970; correspondence, check request, galleys (Box 879)
        - Seaver, Richard, 1970; correspondence from PepsiCo, typescript, galleys (Box 879)
        - Seligson, Tom, 1970; author correspondence, check request, contract, typescript (Box 879)
        - Slater, Philip E., 1970; agent correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, setting copy (taken from another edition), galleys (Box 879)
        - Ungerer, Tomi, 1970; agent correspondence, check request (Box 879)
      - Letters to the editor, 1965; lists, photocopies of clippings, etc. (Box 879)
    - Vol. 14, No. 80 (July 1970)
      - Editorial files
        - Project file, 1970 (Box 879)
        - Beckett, Samuel, 1970; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 879)
        - Bishop, Jordan, 1970; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 879)
        - Bonitzer, Pascal / Delahaye, Michel / Pierre, Sylvie, 1970; check request, typescript (original and photocopy), galleys, issue of Cahiers du Cinema, March 1970 (Box 879)
        - Ginsberg, Allen, 1970; author correspondence, check request, contract, typescript (photocopy), galleys (Box 879)
        - Hennessey, Brian D., 1970; invoice (Box 879)
        - Hentoff, Nat, 1970; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 879)
        - Holmes, John Clellon, 1970; author correspondence, check request, typescript, galleys (Box 879)
        - Krim, Seymour, 1970; author correspondence, clippings (Box 879)
        - Lawrence, J. D. / Springer, Frank, 1970; check request (Box 879)
        - Papaleo, Joseph, 1970; agent correspondence, check request, contract, typescript, galleys (Box 879)
        - Rader, Dotson, 1970; check request, typescript (original and photocopy), galleys (Box 879)
        - Rumaker, Michael, 1970; author correspondence, check request, contract, typescript, galleys (photocopy) (Box 879)
        - Seligson, Tom, 1970; check request, typescript (photocopy), galleys (Box 879)
        - Turner, Frederick W., 1970; publisher correspondence, check request, typescript, galleys (Box 879)
      - Letters to the editor, 1965; lists, photocopies of clippings, etc. (Box 879)
    - Vol. 14, No. 81 (August 1970)
      - Editorial files
        - Project file, 1970 (Box 880)
        - Bishop, Jordan, 1970; author correspondence, check request, contract, typescript (original and photocopy), galleys (Box 880)
        - Blackburn, Richard, 1970; check request, contract, typescript, galleys (Box 880)
        - Boyle, Kay, 1970; agent correspondence, check request, typescript, galleys (Box 880)
        - Carroll, Kent, 1970; check request, typescript (original and photocopy), galleys; 3 folders (Box 880)
        - Carson, L. M. Kit, 1970; check request, contract, typescript (photocopy) (Box 880)
        - Eastlake, William, 1970-1971; check request, typescript, galleys, copyright (Box 880)
        - Henderson, David, 1970-1971; 1973; author correspondence, check request, contract, biographical sheet, typescript (photocopy), galleys (photocopy) (Box 880)
        - Hentoff, Nat, 1970; check request, typescript (photocopy), galleys (Box 880)
        - Lahr, John, 1970; author correspondence, check request, typescript (original and photocopy), galleys (Box 880)
        - Lawrence, J. D. / Springer, Frank, 1970; check request (Box 880)
        - O'Donoghue, Michael, 1970; contract, typescript (Box 880)
        - McCrary, James, 1970; check request, contract, typescript, galleys (Box 880)
        - Steingesser, Martin, 1970; author correspondence, check request, contract, typescript, galleys (Box 880)
      - Letters to the editor, 1965; lists, photocopies of clippings, etc. (Box 880)
    - Vol. 14, No. 82 (September 1970)
      - Editorial files
        - Project file, 1970 (Box 880)
        - Carroll, Kent, 1970; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 880)
        - Carson, L. M. Kit, 1970; author correspondence, check request, contract, typescript (original and photocopy), galleys (Box 880)
        - Gold, Buddy, 1970; invoice (Box 880)
        - Hentoff, Nat, 1970; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 880)
        - Lahr, John, 1970; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 880)
        - Lawrence, J. D. / Springer, Frank, 1970; check request (Box 880)
        - Lester, Julius, 1970; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 880)
        - Manceaux, Michele, 1970; agent correspondence, check request, typescript, galleys (Box 880)
        - Numa, Shozo, 1970; agent correspondence, typescript (photocopy), galleys (Box 880)
        - Roueche, Berton, 1970; agent correspondence, check request, contract, typescript, galleys (Box 880)
        - Schultz, John, 1970; check request, typescript (photocopy), galleys (Box 881)
        - Skir, Leo, 1970; check request, typescript (original and photocopy), galleys (Box 881)
        - Skvorecky, Josef, 1970; check request, typescript, galleys (Box 881)
        - Vian, Boris, 1965; 1970; correspondence with Raymond Federman (translator), check request, typescript (original and photocopy) (Box 881)
        - Wells, Robert, 1970; author correspondence, typescript (photocopy), galleys (photocopy) (Box 881)
      - Letters to the editor, 1965; lists, photocopies of clippings, etc. (Box 881)
    - Vol. 14, No. 83 (October 1970)
      - Editorial files
        - Project file, 1970 (Box 881)
        - Amidon, Bill, 1970; agent correspondence, check request, contract, typescript, galleys (Box 881)
        - Carroll, Kent, [1970]; check request, typescript (photocopy), galleys (Box 881)
        - Corey, L. G., 1970; author correspondence, check request, contract, typescript, galleys (Box 881)